vistage.com 2019-12-27

# Privacy Policy | Vistage

Vistage Worldwide, Inc. and its global subsidiaries and successors (collectively “Vistage”) is committed to protecting the privacy of  individuals who visit our public, private and/or restricted-use Web sites, including but not limited to: www.vistage.com and my.vistage.com (collectively, the “Sites“), as well as individuals who register to use our Services as defined below or who register to attend Vistage events.

This Privacy Policy describes how Vistage collects, uses and shares the personal information we receive or that you make available to us by using our Sites or the applications, services, events and programs offered by Vistage (collectively, the “Services”). It also describes the choices available to you regarding Vistage’s use of your personal information, the steps you can take to access this information and, where applicable, to request that we correct or delete it. We can be contacted by using the details in the “How to contact us” section below.

Vistage may also provide further privacy notices in respect to other interactions with you (for example, specific services requests) and the resultant processing of your personal information.

**Topics:**

  * What information do we collect about you?
  * What is the purpose of us processing your personal information?
  * What is our legal basis for processing your personal information?
  * How will we use the information about you?
  * How do we share information collected? __
  * Communication preferences
  * Access to your information
  * Cookies and Pixel Tags
  * Links to Other Web Sites
  * Changes to This Privacy Policy
  * How to contact us

## What information do we collect about you?

## _Applicable to all Site users:_

Vistage collects personal information about you when you register with any of our Sites or enter into a contract with us for our Services. We also collect personal information when you voluntarily provide personal or business details via online or paper submission forms, surveys, or when you subscribe to Vistage newsletters.

When you express interest in obtaining more information from Vistage, or when you register with one of our Sites, we may ask for personal information such as your name, e-mail address, birth date, gender, zip code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. Additionally, when you visit our Sites, Vistage automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, Vistage cookie information, and the page you request.

_Applicable specifically to Vistage Community Members:_  
When you become a Member, Chair or Speaker (“Vistage Community Member”), Vistage may ask you for additional information, including but not limited to, financial information (e.g. bank details or credit card information) and business details (e.g. company contact information, number of employees in the organization, and company annual revenues).

## What is the purpose of us processing your personal information?

The personal information you have provided to Vistage will be used for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy or any other purposes disclosed in any separate communication. For example, we will use personal information to perform Services requested.  We will also record your use of our Sites to operate and improve the Sites, thus helping us to better understand your needs and interests.

Vistage may retain your personal information for a period of time consistent with the original purpose of collection. For example, we may retain your personal information while your account to use our Sites or Services is active or as necessary for us to administer ongoing obligations.  We also may retain your personal information during the period of time needed for Vistage to pursue our legitimate business interests, conduct audits, comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements.

## What is our legal basis for processing your personal information?

_Applicable to Site users (not including Vistage Community Members):_  
If you are not a Vistage Community Member, the legal basis for processing your personal information is legitimate interest because Vistage benefits commercially from active Members and we may wish to invite you to become a Member.

_Applicable to Vistage Community Members:_  
The legal basis for processing your personal information while you are a Vistage Community Member is necessity to perform our contractual obligations. Additionally we process your business details in our legitimate interest so we can use and store your business details as part of the Vistage Community Member and alumni experience which may enable you to connect with fellow members and Chairs.  This includes our directory of members and Chairs, which is made available to all Vistage Community Members worldwide.

Vistage will also send Communications (defined below), in our legitimate business interest to promote our range of Services and events.

## How will we use the information about you?

_Applicable to all Site users:_  
The personal information that you have provided to us will be used for the purposes described above, including as mentioned, to enable Vistage to provide the Services you have requested.

Your personal information may also be used to send additional information about Vistage’s Services, updates, promotions and events (“Communications”) unless you opt out from receiving such Communications. We will seek your advance permission to send Communications if legally required.

_Applicable to Vistage Community Members:_  
If you are a Vistage Community Member, in addition to the uses applicable to all Site users, your personal information will be used to administer your account and enable you to connect with fellow members and Chairs.  This includes our directory of members and Chairs, which is made available to all Vistage Community Members worldwide.

## How do we share information collected?

Vistage may share your personal information with affiliates for purposes related to customer support, technical operation, and account management.

We may also make your personal information available to authorized third parties so they can act on our behalf to assist in providing Services. Authorized third parties include service providers (e.g. Salesforce), contractors (e.g. Chairs), business partners, and third parties that that collect cookies (e.g. Google Analytics). These authorized third parties will use your personal information solely for the purpose of providing services to Vistage. For example, Communications may advertise Vistage events and Services, some of which are offered to you in partnership with specially selected partners of Vistage (e.g. Stanford Business School). Because of this, your personal information may be shared with them solely for the purpose of assisting Vistage to inform you of Vistage events and Services.  
Vistage does not otherwise rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except when we have your permission, or when required by law, in the exercise our legal rights or defense against legal claims, to effect a merger or acquisition of a Vistage entity, to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding actual or suspected illegal or malicious activities, or to address actual or suspected violations of Vistage’s Terms of Use, Confidentiality Pledge and Standards.

## International transfer of information collected

To facilitate Vistage’s global operations, we transfer and access personal information from around the world.  Primary storage of personal information collected is in the United States. We take precautions to keep your personal information secure and maintain physical, electronic, contractual and procedural safeguards (e.g. model clauses) that comply with applicable law.

When you become a Vistage Community Member, your personal details will be visible to the international Vistage Community network. You may update visibility preferences at any time by logging into your personal account on my.vistage.com and selecting the “Edit profile & privacy” link.

## Access to your information

Vistage acknowledges that you may have the right to be informed about our processing of your personal information, restrict or object to certain processing, as well as access to your data, or the right to correct, amend, or delete data that relates to you.  We aim to keep the personal information we hold about you accurate and up to date. If at any time, you want to verify, update, amend or delete any personal information we hold about you please contact us using the information in the “How to contact us” section below.  
If you are a resident of the European Union (EU) and have an unresolved privacy or personal information collection, use, or disclosure concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact the EU Data Protection Authorities. For more information on how to contact the EU Data Protection Authorities, [click here](http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/article-29/structure/data-protection-authorities/index_en.htm).

## Communication Preferences

You may manage your receipt of Communications via email by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link located on the bottom of Vistage emails. Additionally, you may opt out of Communications by emailing us at: [privacy@vistage.com](mailto:privacy@vistage.com).

Vistage will retain some of your personal information to know not to contact you again in the future.

## Cookies & Pixel Tags

We collect visitor information by using cookies and pixel tags.

## Cookies

Cookies are files or pieces of information that may be stored in your computer’s hard drive when you visit a Web site. This file or piece of information allows a user to move quickly and easily around our Sites and is used to identify returning users. We also use a cookie to track a user’s sessions. We use this information to find out what site features are most popular so we can develop our Sites and content.

The use of cookies is an industry standard and commonly done on websites. We do not, however, use cookies to retrieve involuntary information about your computer.

Accordingly, if you would prefer, you can set up your browser to refuse cookies or to alert you to their presence and thereby allow you to remove them from your computer. If you reject cookies, you may have difficulty navigating parts of our website, and may need to enter identifying information each time you access a password protected page.

We use the following categories of cookies on our website:

##### **Strictly Necessary Cookies**

These cookies are essential in order to enable you to move around the Sites and use its features, such as accessing secure areas of the Sites and using Vistage’s Services. Since these cookies are essential to operate Vistage’s Sites and Services, there is no option to opt out of these cookies.

##### **Performance Cookies**

These cookies collect information about how visitors use our Sites, for instance which pages visitors go to most often. These cookies don’t collect information that identifies a visitor. All information these cookies collect is aggregated and therefore anonymous. It is only used to improve how a website works.

##### **Functionality Cookies**

Functionality cookies remember information you have entered or choices you make (e.g. your username, preferred language, region), and provide enhanced, more personal features. They may also be used to provide services you have asked for such as watching a video or commenting on a blog. The information these cookies collect may be anonymized and they cannot track your browsing activity on other websites.

##### **Advertising Cookies**

These cookies are used to make advertising more relevant to you and your interests. They are also used to limit the number of times you see an advertisement as well as help measure the effectiveness of advertising campaigns. The cookies are usually placed by third party advertising networks. They remember the websites you visit and that information is shared with other parties such as advertisers.

To manage the use of any of these cookies on our Sites or to opt out of their use (except for the Strictly Necessary Cookies), click “Cookies Preference Center” at the bottom of this page.  Please note that opting out of any of these cookies may impact your use of our Sites.

## Pixel tag

A pixel tag, also known as a clear GIF or web beacon, is an invisible tag or tiny graphic image placed on certain pages of our website or in emails but not on your computer. When you access these pages, pixel tags generate a generic notice of that visit. They usually work in conjunction with cookies, registering when a particular computer visits a particular page. If you turn off cookies the pixel tag will simply detect an anonymous website visit. Pixel tags help us analyze our visitors’ online behavior and measure the effectiveness of our websites and our advertising. We work with service providers that help us track, collect, and analyze this information.

Pixel tags on our sites may be used to collect information about your visit, including the pages you view, the features you use, the links you click, and other actions you take in connection with the Sites. This information may include your computer’s Internet protocol (IP) address, your browser type, your operating system, date and time information, and other technical information about your computer. We may also track certain information about the identity of the websites you visit immediately before and after coming to our site. We do not otherwise track any information about your use of other websites.

Pixel tags and cookies in our emails may be used to track your interactions with those messages, such as when you receive, open, or click a link in an email message from us.

We also work with third-party companies that use tracking technologies to serve advertisements on our behalf across the Internet. These companies may collect information about your visits to our websites and your interaction with our advertising and other communications.

We may combine the information we collect through cookies and pixel tags with other information we have collected from you. In Vistage’s legitimate business interest, this information may be used to improve our websites, to personalize your online experience, to tailor our Communications with you, to determine the effectiveness of our advertising, and for other internal business purposes.

## Links to Other Web Sites

Our Sites contain links to other third party websites; however, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites and do not make any representation as to the existence, sufficiency, accuracy or completeness of such websites or the privacy policies of such websites. Please see the website’s privacy policy for more information on the website owner’s data protection practices.

## Changes to This Privacy Policy

Vistage may update this Privacy Policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary e-mail address we have on file for you or by placing a prominent notice on the applicable Site(s).

## How to contact us

**Vistage has appointed a Data Protection Officer (DPO) who is responsible for overseeing questions related to this Privacy Policy. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy please contact the DPO:**

  * By email: [privacy@vistage.com](mailto:privacy@vistage.com)
  * Or write us at:

Vistage Worldwide, Inc.  
Attention: Data Protection Officer  
4840 Eastgate Mall  
San Diego, CA 92121
